这是他们生产的最棒的飞机
It's, like, the best one they make,
- 我就是没法让它飞起来  - 我来想办法
- I just can't get it to work.  - I'll figure it out.
它飞起来的时候 可以把高清视频直接导入你的手机
It streams HD video straight to your phone while it's flying.
真棒
Nice.
我单身的时候 你在哪里?
Where were you when I was single?
好了 再过一个小时就要出发了 行李收拾好了吗?
Okay, we should leave in about an hour. You all packed?
好了 我只需要再放几样东西进去...
Uh, yeah, I just need to throw in a few last minute things...
你懂的 化妆品 内衣和衣服
you know, makeup, underwear, clothes.
如果你可以把浴室地板
If your bathroom floor
打包带上飞机 那你就算收好了
counts as a carry-on, you're packed.
Leonard 你以前做过
Leonard, have you ever given
高中毕业典礼演讲吗?
a high school commencement speech before?
没有 这太令人兴奋了
Nope. It's pretty exciting.
你就不怕被弄瞎吗?
Aren't you afraid of being blinded?
我怎么会被弄瞎?
How would I be blinded?
毕业典礼结束的时候
At the end of the ceremony,
所有学生会把带尖角的帽子抛到空中
all the students throw those pointy hats in the air.
虽然场面好看
It's all pomp and circumstance
迟早有人会被戳瞎的
until someone loses an eye.
我愿意冒险
I'll take my chances.
好吧
Fine.
不知道有没有
I wonder if they make
用盲文做"我早告诉过你"的卡片
"I told you so" cards in braille.
听着 毕业典礼演讲的问题
Look, the problem with commencement speeches
就在于太无聊了
is that they're boring.
你有T恤衫大炮吗?
Ooh, do you own a T-shirt cannon?
他怎么会有T恤衫大炮?
Why would he own a T-shirt cannon?
我不知道 我为什么就有呢?
I don't know. Why do I own one?
我觉得你能和Penny
I think it's really nice
分享这次经历真是太棒了
that you're sharing this experience with Penny.
我觉得带她故地重游
Mm, I thought it'd be fun
一定会很有趣
to show her my old stomping grounds.
我还记得他们欺负我的确切位置
I even know the exact spot where they used to stomp me.
现在你是个成功的科学家
Well, now you get to go back
要荣归母校
as a successful scientist.
还带这个漂亮姑娘
With a beautiful girl on your arm.
还有帽子尖 插在眼球上
And a pointy hat sticking out of your eyeball.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第八季第22集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 提拉米酥
校对: UU酸乳
翻译: 影森林 肉慕斯 奥利奥 提拉米酥
你怎么这么快就准备好了?
How'd you get ready so fast?
我没带多少东西
Oh, I pack light.
有一次 我一件长T恤和一根皮带
Once, I got through an entire spring break
就撑过了整个春假
with nothing but a long T-shirt and a belt.
皮带是拿来做什么的?
Why did you need a belt?
用它来搭配夜生活妆容的
It's called an evening look.
我从没去过新泽西州
I've never been to New Jersey before.
"泽西海岸"和"比弗利娇妻"
It gets a bad rap from shows
这些剧里对新泽西州的评价很差
like Jersey Shore and Real Housewives.
但那都不是真的吧?
So it's not really like that?
不 都是真的
No, it's like that.
我真的很高兴能带你逛逛
Well, I'm excited to show you around.
你觉得我们会有时间去拜访你妈妈吗?
You think we'll have time to visit your mom over there?
有 我们还会有时间用压蒜器把我的旧东西都碾碎了
Yes. We'll also have time to put my junk in a garlic press,
但这两件事 我都不会做
but I'm not doing that either.
糟了
Uh-oh.
我收到了提醒
I just got an alert.
我们的航班被取消了
Our flight's been canceled.
什么?
What?
好像是东海岸那边
Yeah, looks like there's a big storm
遭遇了大风暴
all up the East Coast.
我们能换个航班吗?
Well, can we get on another airline?
我觉得不能
I don't think so.
那就这样了?
So, that's it?
我们不去了?
We're not going?
我觉得去不了了
I guess not.
太糟糕了
Well, that sucks.
对
Yeah.
我还认真准备了演讲稿
I worked hard on that speech, too.
你可以跟我说一遍
Oh. You could tell it to me.
谢谢 不过我没事
Oh, thank you, but I'm okay.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
我可以假装自己是个看到优秀校友
I could pretend I'm a high school cheerleader
就把持不住的高中啦啦队队长
who can't control herself around esteemed alumni.
尊敬的啦啦队队员们 你们好
Greetings, distinguished cheerleaders.
哇哦!
Ooh!
好了 无线网中继器已打开 摄像头已打开
Okay, the WiFi extender is on, the camera's on,
它们用的是同一个网络
they're both on the same network;
我们应该能看到影像了
we should be getting an image.
我只看到了黑屏
All I see is a black screen.
还有我的倒影
And my own reflection.
我看上去很伤心
I look sad.
也许我们应该重新校准一下
Maybe we should recalibrate it.
- 好吧  - 第一步:
- All right.  - Step one:
快速将校准开关
rapidly flip the calibration switch
上下最大范围内拨动
from the fully up to the fully down positions
至少十次
for at least ten times.
竟然写了"至少"?
It actually says "at least"?
对
Yeah.
他们干嘛要写"至少"?
Why would they say "at least"?
切换十次?
Is it ten toggles?
还是切换一百次? 你懂吗?
Is it 100 toggles? You know?
还是一千次?
Is it 1,000 toggles?
一万次? 十万次?
10,000 toggles? 100,000 toggles?
Sheldon 别说了!
Sheldon!
你明白我想表达什么意思吧
You see where I'm going with this.
你就拨动开关
Just flip the switch
直到模型机上的灯变成黄色
until the lights on the drone change to solid yellow.
好 那倒是挺简单的
All right, that seems simple enough.
校准程序启动
Initiating calibration sequence.
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four,
五 六 七 八 九 十
five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
我觉得十次也能算在"至少十次"里吧
Well, I suppose ten is technically "at least ten."
但是他们还是会收到"至少"一封投诉信的
But they're still getting at least one angry letter.
现在我要以它的中轴为中心水平旋转
Now I rotate it horizontally
直到灯变成绿色
on its center axis until the lights turn green.
初始化旋转程序
Initiating rotation sequence.
不要盯着我看 初始化它
Don't look at me, initiate.
哦... 又红又黄是什么意思?
Oh... What does red and yellow mean?
意思是校准失败了
It means the calibration failed.
我们得重来
We have to start over.
嗯 好吧
Oh. Very well.
重启校准程序
Reinitiating calibration sequence.
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four,
五 六 七 八 九 十...
five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten...
十一
eleven.
还好我没有给他们写投诉信
It's a good thing I didn't send that letter.
嗯 你好 爸爸 什么事?
Mm. Hello, Daddy. What's up?
没什么 就是想看看我儿子最近怎么样
Not much, just wanted to see how my son's doing.
我很好 谢谢
Very well, thank you.
你还在和那个皮肤科医生约会吗?
Are you still dating that dermatologist?
如果你可以感觉到我柔软的皮肤的话
If you could feel how soft my skin is,
你就不会这么问了
you wouldn't have to ask.
这样啊 我还有些别的事要问你
Oh, and there's something else I wanted to ask you.
为什么你把一个月的房租都花在了一个玩具直升机上?
Why did you spend a month's rent on a toy helicopter?!
哦 原来账单寄到你那里了啊
Oh, you're where that bill goes.
我受不了资助你这种愚蠢的生活方式了
I'm tired of indulging your foolish lifestyle.
是时候该让你自己有些责任感了
It's time you learned responsibility.
而唯一的办法就是
And the only way to teach you that
切断我们给你的生活费
is to cut off your allowance.
不要啊 爸爸 别这样!
No, Daddy, no!
还有好多种让我体会责任感的方法呢
There are lots of other ways to teach me responsibility.
我知道 你可以给我一个鸡蛋
I know, you can give me an egg
然后让我把它完好无损地保管一个星期!
and make me take care of it for a week!
我不会的 我已经下定决心了
No, my mind is made up.
从现在开始 你要靠你自己挣钱了
Starting now, you're on your own.
但 爸爸 我 我很想你们啊
But, Daddy, I-I miss my family so much,
你又和妈妈离婚了
and with you and Mummy getting a divorce,
我现在感到又伤心又寂寞
I feel sad and empty.
我买的那个玩具
Buying a little toy
填补了我最近的空虚感
every now and then helps me fill that void.
当我不能每天拥抱你的时候
So while I can't hug you every day,
玩那个直升机时我会...
flying that helicopter...
我要挂断了
I'm cutting you off.
明确一下 你是要断生活费还是断我这句话啊?
Just to be clear, financially or mid-sentence?
没有红和黄
No red and yellow,
No red and yellow.
耶! 它绿了!
Yay! It's green!
我们成功了!
We did it!
太好了!
Oh!
天哪 如果光是旋转都这么好玩 想象一下他飞起来的样子吧
God, if it's this much fun to rotate, imagine when we fly it.
好 现在我要做的就是垂直地旋转它
Okay, now all I have to do is rotate it vertically
直到灯灭了
until the lights turn off.
哦 不 哦
Oh, no! Oh!
好吧 游戏结束了
All right, playtime's over.
我们把这个宝贝疙瘩拆开吧
Let's open this baby up.
这不会把保修作废吗?
Won't that void the warranty?
Sheldon 我可是有工程硕士学位的人
Sheldon, I have a master's degree in engineering.
保修什么的都是给我擦屁股的
I wipe my bottom with warranties.
除了苹果公司的保修
Except for AppleCare.
这是个一劳永逸的保修
That pays for itself in the long run.
嗨
Hi.
嗨 你去哪了?
Hey, where'd you go?
我给你买了一些小玩意哄你开心
I got you a little something to cheer you up.
真的吗?
Really?
昨天晚上的啪啪啪 今天早上的煎饼...
Sex last night, pancakes this morning...
我是要死了吗?
Am I dying?
快打开它吧
Just open it.
学士服和学士帽?
A cap and gown?
我要这些干嘛?
Why do I need a cap and gown?
因为你要做毕业演讲啊
Because you are giving your commencement speech.
你说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
我给你以前的高中打了电话
I called your old high school
说服他们让你通过Skype来演讲了
and convinced them to let you give your speech over Skype.
真的吗?
Really?
太棒了!
That's amazing!
你还给我买了这个学士服让我开心
And you gave me the robes to give it in.
谢谢你
Thank you.
嗯 其实这些衣服...
Yeah, now about those...
是我从道具店里买来的
uh, they came from a costume shop,
他们剩下的只有性感毕业生系列的了
and all they had left was sexy graduate,
所以...
so they...
衣服可能有些短
might be a little short.
短小性感 这才是我的特长嘛
Short and sexy, that's my wheelhouse.
那必须!
Yeah!
天哪 天哪 好多零件啊
Boy, oh, boy, that's a lot of pieces.
你都知道他们是干什么用的 对吗?
You know what they all do, right?
当然
Yes, of course.
那这个是干什么用的?
What about this one?
嗯 我... 你对微型集成电路
Well, I... how familiar are you
熟不熟呢?
with miniaturized integrated logic circuits?
并不熟
Not very.
那里不就是个微型
That right there is a miniaturized
集成电路吗?
integrated logic circuit.
所以说 你能修好它吗?
So, can you get it working?
我可是麻省理工出来的工程师诶
I'm an MIT-trained engineer.
我还给空间站造零件呢
I've built components for the space station.
我还以为空间站的零重力厕所不怎么好用啊
I thought the zero-gravity toilet didn't work.
它很好用
It worked fine,
只是它们不是为俄罗斯宇航员和
it just wasn't designed for Russian cosmonauts
他们以土豆为主食的饮食习惯设计的
and their potato-based diet.
嗨 伙计们
Hey, guys.
- 嗨  - 你好啊
- Hey.  - Hello.
我得把直升机退回去了 我爹...
I have to return the helicopter. My father...
你都做了什么?！
What did you do?!
啊 不要担心
Well, don't worry.
他是麻省理工毕业的
He went to MIT.
只要不是从俄罗斯人直肠里面出来的问题
He can solve any problem,
他都能解决
as long as it doesn't originate in a Russian man's colon.
真不敢相信你这么做!
I don't freaking believe this!
别急 搞得定的
Relax, it'll be fine.
不 你要把它马上组装好
No, you have to put this back together
我好拿去退!
right now, so I can return it!
你退不了
You can't return it.
Howard拿保修卡擦屁股了
Howard wiped his bottom with the warranty.
什么?!
What?!
可能只是个比喻
I think metaphorically.
但他确实在洗手间里待了一会儿
But he was in the bathroom for a while.
Howard 我爸断我生活费了
Howard, my father cut me off.
我得把买这个的钱退回来!
I have to get my money back for this!
别激动
Calm down.
好吧
Okay.
好吧 你说得对
Okay, you're right.
是时候站起来
It's time for me to step up
对自己的生活负责了
and take responsibility for my life.
做个男人
Be a man.
喂 老妈
Hello, Mummy.
你好啊 Rajesh
Hello, Rajesh.
多么贴心的惊喜啊
What a nice surprise.
我最近挺想你的
Well, I've been thinking about you.
你还好吗?
How are you doing?
开心吗 老妈?
Are you happy, Mummy?
你这样问候 真是贴心啊
Such a sweet boy for asking.
都不敢相信你是你爸的毒苗
Can't believe you come from the poison seed of your father.
我比较喜欢认为自己是遗传你的
Well, I like to think I take mostly after you.
总之 说到老爸
Anyway, speaking of Daddy,
我之前跟他有段很奇怪的谈话
I had a very strange conversation with him.
他说他没钱给我生活费了
He said he couldn't afford to send me money anymore
因为他的社交太频繁
because of his active social life.
他什么意思 "社交频繁"?
What does that mean, "active social life"?
还是不聊他了
Well, let's not talk about him
管他在耍什么把戏呢
or whatever shenanigans he may or may not be up to.
聊聊你吧
Let's talk about you.
Rajesh 你爸在见别的女人吗?
Rajesh, is your father seeing someone?
老妈 我只知道
All I know, Mummy, is that
他是个单身阔绰的医生 而现在不知为何
he's a single wealthy doctor, and now, for some reason,
没钱给你的宝贝儿子了
there's no money for your little boy.
不管你爸给你多少钱
Well, however much money your father was giving you,
我都加倍给你
I'll give you more.
多谢啦 老妈 爱你哟!
Thank you, Mummy, I love you!
大伙每人一架直升飞机!
Helicopters for everybody!
为什么这么磨蹭?
What's taking so long?
我觉得这可能行不通
I don't think this is gonna work.
出来让我看看
Just let me see.
亲爱的 你知道毕业礼服里面
Sweetie, you know you're supposed to wear clothes
要穿衣服的吧
underneath a graduation gown.
首先 你居然知道这点
A: surprised you know that.
其次 我想让你看见一个性感毕业生
B: I wanted to look like a sexy graduate for you.
哦
Oh.
的确很性感
Well, you do.
哦 谢啦
Oh. Thank you.
嗯
Yeah.
你是视频演讲 他们看不见你的下半身
You're gonna be on Skype; they're not gonna see your legs.
我还是穿上裤子吧 以防万一
Well, I'm gonna go put on some pants just in case.
但我不得不说 这样很自在哦
But I have to say, this is very freeing.
系条腰带 姐带你兜个风
Add a belt and I'll take you someplace nice.
哦
Oh.
成交 搞定
Done and done.
好了 我大概锁定了故障范围
Okay, I think I've narrowed it down
板载通信芯片上有个小针脚坏了
to a faulty pin on the onboard communication chip.
有一手嘛
Very impressive.
那个 你修完手上的
You know, when you're done with that,
顺便看一眼这个吧?
can you look at this?
这家伙不冒烟了
It doesn't make smoke anymore.
一个一个来
One toy at a time.
嗯 抱歉
Mm. Sorry.
啊 或许这样也好吧
Ah, maybe it's for the best.
我听说火车烟尘
I hear locomotive smoke
是火车爱好者的第二大杀手
is the second leading cause of death among train aficionados.
第一大杀手是什么?
What's the first one?
自杀
Suicide.
错
Wrong.
是肥胖症
Obesity.
我给你带了你要的工具
I have the tool you wanted.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们大伙不用费这么大劲去修它
You guys don't have to go to the trouble.
老子现在又有钱了
I'm back in the money now;
我可以买架新的直升飞机模型
I can just buy another helicopter.
不是钱的问题
It's not about the money.
而是要如何解决问题
It's about solving a problem.
这也是我立志当工程师的原因
It's why I became an engineer.
我喜欢做这个 也在训练自己这方面的能力
It's what I like to do, it's what I'm trained to do.
我为此而生
It's who I am.
看看你... 无所不能的小工程师
Oh, look at you... the little engineer that could.
为什么不打客服求助技术支持?
Why don't you just call tech support?
- 嘿!  - 哇哦  - 别这样!
- Hey!  - Whoa!  - Not cool!
怎么了?
What?
这世界上有两种人:
There's two kinds of people in this world:
一种是求助客服的人
those who call tech support
另一种是嘲笑第一种人的人
and those who make fun of the people who call tech support.
我向来都是求助客服的
I call tech support all the time.
哈哈! 你居然求助客服!
Ha-ha! You call tech support!
你小学生啊!
What a baby!
现在有请毕业典礼演讲嘉宾
And now, for our commencement address,
我们的杰出校友之一
one of our most distinguished alumni,
著名加州理工物理学家Leonard Hofstadter博士
noted Caltech physicist Dr. Leonard Hofstadter.
尊敬的老师同学们
Members of the faculty, students,
今天 我很高兴能为你们演讲
I'm excited to speak to you today.
我至今还对自己
I can't help but remember
坐在礼堂时的那刻记忆犹新
the last time I was in this auditorium.
两个长曲棍球队的家伙
Two guys from the lacrosse team
把我的哮喘吸入器扔来扔去
played keep-away with my asthma inhaler.
不多说我这十周年同学会了
But enough about my ten-year reunion.
现在我想花上几分钟
I'd also like to take a moment
感谢我美丽的未婚妻
to thank my beautiful fiancée
本来由于天气原因 我无法到场
for to helping make this speech possible,
是她让我今天能有机会做这场演讲
even though weather nearly prevented it.
哦 大家好
Oh. Hello.
我... 我没想到他会把摄像头对着我
I... I didn't know he was gonna point it at me,
那个... 别嗑药 别逃学
so... don't do drugs and stay in school.
他们已经毕业了
They're graduating.
好吧 再见!
Okay, bye!
电路已经连接好了
All right, the power supply is reconnected.
我们差不多搞定了
I think we're back in business.
只要再做几次测试 就可以去室外了
Let's just run a few tests before we take it outside.
- Sheldon 无线网状态?  - 已连接
- Sheldon, we got WiFi?  - Check.
- 全球定位系统?  - 已连接
- GPS?  - Check.
- 电池电量?  - 已充电
- Battery charged?  - Check.
白白浪费了四个小时? 已浪费
Four hours of our lives gone? Check.
好了
All right.
准备就绪
All systems go.
五...
In five...
四 三 二 一
four, three, two, one.
我的火车以前就是这么喷气的
That's what my train used to do.
准备给售后服务打电话了吗?
Ready to call tech support?
把号码给我吧
Give me the number.
估计结果就是
Probably wind up
某个老外接起电话
talking to some foreign guy
读着我手里的手册
who's reading from the same manual I have.
(印度人客服的梗)
是我老爸 你们想多了
It's my father, you jerks.
喂 老爸
Hello, Daddy.
你跟你妈说什么了?
What did you say to your mother?
没说什么啊
Nothing.
就是问问
I was just calling to check in,
她最近怎么样
make sure she's doing okay.
你给她打过电话之后
Well, after talking to you,
她好像觉得我是那种花花公子
she seems to think I'm some sort of playboy.
是嘛?
Really?
我也不知道她怎么会这么想
I don't know where she'd get an idea like that.
你也知道 老妈脑袋里总是有奇奇怪怪的想法
You know Mummy and her crazy imagination.
真高兴我比较像你
I'm so lucky I take after you.
你觉得你像我?
You think you take after me?
我一直试着向你学习
Well, I try to.
要不是把你当做榜样
I certainly wouldn't be a scientist
我一定不会成为科学家的
if you hadn't been my role model.
谁想坐真的直升机去拉斯维加斯玩?!
Who wants to go to Vegas in a real helicopter?!
(美国作家 代表作"绿野仙踪")
L. Frank Baum曾说过
It was L. Frank Baum who said,
"无论是多么技术高超的小偷 都无法偷走一个人的知识
"No thief, however skillful, can rob one of knowledge,
所以知识是一个人最宝贵也最安全的财富"
and that is why knowledge is the best and safest treasure."
天啊 我自己都觉得无聊
Wow, I'm boring myself.
不好意思 我现在看不到你们的表情
Sorry, I can't see any of your faces right now,
不过估计都是这样的
but I bet they look like this.
呃 我... 我写了很长的演讲稿
Uh, you know, I... I wrote an entire speech
想告诉你们高中对你们的影响有多大
to say how high school prepares you
还有高中是个多好的地方
and what a wonderful place it is,
可是我讨厌高中
but I hated it.
可能如果你长的这么漂亮的话 应该过的还不错...
Maybe high school's great if you look like this...
不过我都不觉得我在那所学校上过学
but I didn't even feel like I existed at that school.
现在想起来
And now that I think about it,
我敢说你们当中的很多人应该都有这感觉
I bet a lot of you feel the same way.
所以 我后面的演讲
So, for the remainder of my speech,
是说给那些不受关注的孩子们的
this is for the invisible kids.
呃 可能你们从来都格格不入
Uh, maybe you never fit in.
或者你可能是个子最矮的学生
Or maybe you're the smallest kid in the school,
也可能是是最胖的或者最怪的
or the heaviest or the weirdest.
可能你直到毕业
Maybe you're graduating
都还没有经历过初吻
and you still haven't had your first kiss.
对了 十九岁
By the way, 19;
Geraldine Coco 不管你现在在哪里 我都想对你说声谢谢
and Geraldine Coco, wherever you are, thank you.
可能你连一个朋友都没有
Maybe you don't have any friends.
相信我 这都无所谓
And guess what? That's okay.
当那些受欢迎的同学都在...
While all the popular kids are off doing...
管它呢 我从来不知道他们都在干什么
whatever, I don't know what they were doing
因为他们从来不带我玩...
because I was never there...
我... 我一会告诉你
I'll... I'll tell you later.
重点是
My point is,
你独自一人的时候
while you're spending all this time on your own,
可以研究研究电脑或者练练大提琴
building computers or practicing your cello,
你做的事情都会变得有趣起来
what you're really doing is becoming interesting.
而当人们最终注意到你的时候
And when people finally do notice you,
他们会发现 你比他们想象的厉害多了
they're gonna find someone a lot cooler than they thought.
至于那些在高中过的风生水起的学生 我想说
And for those of you who were popular in high school,
很遗憾 高中结束了
it's over, sorry.
感谢大家 并祝贺大家顺利毕业
Thank you and congratulations.
我们非常重视您的来电
Your call is important to us.
我们的技术人员正在忙碌中
All our technicians are busy helping other customers.
请不要挂机
Please stay on the line
我们会尽快为您服务
and someone will be with you shortly.
我这是怎么了?
What happened to me?
我什么时候变成一个
When did I become an old man
对高科技无能为力的老头了?
baffled by modern technology?
接下来
Next thing you know,
我就该把裤子提到胸口
I'll be hitching my pants up to my armpits
还不停地抱怨
and complaining about
年轻人爱听的可怕的音乐
the awful music the kids are listening to.
确实挺可怕的吧?
It is awful, isn't it?
这简直是噪音
Listen to that noise.
等下 等下
Hang on, hang on.
它启动了! 我成功了!
It's working! I did it!
你干了什么?
How'd you do that?
不知道 但是我成功了!
No idea, but I did it!
你是不是不应该让它在房间里飞
Maybe you shouldn't be flying it inside.
我没让它飞!
Well, I'm not flying it!
- 那谁在操控它?  - 我不知道!
- Then who is?  - I don't know!
肯定是从别的地方收到了无线网信号!
Must be getting a WiFi signal from somewhere else!
启动降落程序! 启动降落程序!
Initiate landing sequence! Initiate landing sequence!
嘿 摄像机还开着呢!
Hey, the camera's working!
看啊 是我
Oh, look, it's me.
您好 有什么可以帮您的吗?
Tech Support, may I help you?
喂 机器人在攻击我们! 快报警!
Yes, it's a robot uprising! Call the police!
你真觉得他们喜欢我的演讲?
So you really think they liked it?
亲爱的 这是我听过的最...
Oh, sweetie, it was the best speech I...
别担心 我们这里很安全
Don't worry, everyone in here is safe.